in the near term India is one unique
Market in power say power in the power
because the power demand is growing and
the country is transitioning for thermal
to renewable source currently more solar
and wind I think that is the biggest
story for now and you would have seen
the lot of private companies are into
that space which are putting up solar
plant uh wind wind power plants and also
round the Round the Clock power which is
hybrid of solar and uh and wind also the
usage of batteries increasing I think
there a lot of EX opportunities in the
Renewables place because the power
capacities are going to grow there
significantly for next 3 to 5 years uh I
do want to understand from you uh ra how
are you feeling about the market and the
fact that it's slowly grinding lower we
had uh Prine jagani from U International
yesterday say that there is more
downside that is too open for the
markets and maybe at maybe maybe during
the mid of 2025 uh that's June July of
2025 there would be an entry point to
get back into the markets because right
now domestic investors are also being a
bit wor about growth prospects and
earnings prospects sure so I was
recently in India and I would say that
domestic investors they kept ping money
they kept buying the decline but it's
been 4 and a half months and the
Market's been grinding lower so their
Spirits are a bit down but I have to say
this all depends on uh the flows the
foreign outflows is impact after effect
the foreign outflows that has happened
see over last 4 and a half months of
foreign Out close at $2 billion it's a
significant number and this has happened
that more tactical right foreigners are
not selling because they're giving up on
the India story sure they're selling
because China looks more cheap so they
want to redeploy there sure I think uh
that's that's correct and I think that
kind of fortif is the case that I'm
going to lay out see they the the
foreigners sold from India $2 million
China looked at China go stimulus
Sometime Late September early October
Indian earning slow Indian earning slow
a result of the tighter fiscal policy
and Tighter monetary policy now let's
look at those segments the the fiscal
policy remains tight but as you are
aware that there have been a significant
stimulus for consumption that is given
so I think that area of the market
should do well and secondly RBI is now
uh ramping up Liquid liquidity and uh
cutting rates to boost the credit demand
and growth so I think that should play
out over next three to four months in
the very short term given US dollar and
US tariff Tantrums there can be
volatility but but in our view after 15%
correction this slower earning growth is
now in the price the valuation has
returned to the average so going forward
the on the balance on the other hand the
growth the Confluence of positiv that is
building up which is the tax cut RBS
policies rural growth showing some of
revivals those are not so much in the
price of the positioning but that will
take two to 3 months to play out two to
3 months to play out so uh what happens
next I mean what what are you advising
clients in terms of where are you
deploying cash in India right now where
are you going overweight where are you
underweight where you taking profits how
you rebalancing your portfol in India so
that's a very important question in fact
I think uh throughout last year we kind
of highlighted that we are we were
cautious on the industrial side of the
uh market and uh that's because of a
view that capex LE growth cannot
continue for a long time and uh that has
got playing out so I think for India
there's a significant policy pivot from
capex to consumption and the portfolio
have to reflect the same in that meu I
think we like Auto stocks we like retail
landlords because the ril stocks are
quite expensive we also like large
consumer finance companies in the
unsecured space as well as a secured
rural space